{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Constant head permeability test can be used for ___________.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Coarse-grained soil",
        "b": "Highly permeable soil",
        "c": "Clayey soil",
        "d": "All of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following formula is used in Constant head permeability test?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Jacky’s formula",
        "b": "Louden’s formula",
        "c": "Darcy’s law",
        "d": "Kozney’s formula"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "In constant head permeability test apparatus, the water head at any time instant is equal to ____________.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Difference in the water level in manometers",
        "b": "Cross-sectional area of pipe",
        "c": "Height of permeameter",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "In constant permeability test, the length of specimen is measured by ___________.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Using measuring scale",
        "b": "Calculating the difference in water level",
        "c": "Using Piezometric tube",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The constant head permeability test is used for ___________.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Fine-grained soil",
        "b": "Saturated soil",
        "c": "Clay soil",
        "d": "Coarse-grained soil"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The laboratory observation constant head test consist of measurements of ____________.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Delta H and discharge Q",
        "b": "Only t1 and t2",
        "c": "h1 at an interval of t1 and h2 at an interval of t2",
        "d": "All of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following tubes are used in the constant head test?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Inlet tube",
        "b": "Overflow tube",
        "c": "Outlet tube",
        "d": "All of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the range of permeability of sandy soil in cm/hr.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "0.001 to 0.01",
        "b": "0.01 to 0.1",
        "c": "0.1 to 1",
        "d": "1 to 10"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the device used to measure the head difference in the permeameter",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Manometer",
        "b": "Barometer",
        "c": "Hydrometer",
        "d": "Anemometer"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Why is a steady flow in outlet important while conducting the experiment?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "To ensure laminar flow",
        "b": "To make sure the velocity of water through the soil is constant at all sections",
        "c": "To ensure the inflow of water has constant head",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    }
  ]
}
